Guide to the Mann Library records, 1908-2011.
Mann Library records, 1908-2011
- Series V. Meeting Minutes, Reports, and Statistics
  - Mann Library Council, 1982- 1984 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Request for Proposals for An Integrated Library System for CUL, 1984 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Request for Proposal-Mann Library Automation Study, August 20, 1983 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Requirements Report for Automation Systems and Services, November, 1983 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Requirements Report for Automation Systems and Services, November, 1983 (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - SUNY Council of Head Librarians Executive Committee- Correspondence, Memos, Minutes, 1971-1975 (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - SUNY Council of Head Librarians Executive Committee- Correspondence, Memos, Minutes, 1976-1978 (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - SUNY Council of Head Librarians Executive Committee- Correspondence, Memos, Minutes, 1976-1978 (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - SUNY Council of Head Librarians Executive Committee- Correspondence, Memos, Minutes, 1980-1982 (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - Task Force Documentation (Pt. 1), March 1984 (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - Task Force Documentation (Pt. 2), March 1984 (Box 20, Folder 22)
  - Task Force Documentation (Pt. 3), 1984 (Box 20, Folder 23)
  - Task Force Documentation (Pt. 4), 1984 (Box 20, Folder 24)
  - Task Force Documentation (Pt. 5), 1984 (Box 20, Folder 25)
  - Task Force Documentation (Pt. 6), 1984 (Box 20, Folder 26)
  - NOTIS Response to CUL (Pt. 3- Pt. 7)(Incomplete), August 31, 1984 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Biblio-Techniques-Correspondence, Memos, Reports, 1986 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Biblio-Techniques-Correspondence, Memos, Reports, 1986 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Biblio-Techniques-Correspondence, Memos, Reports, 1984 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Biblio-Techniques-Correspondence, Memos, Reports, 1985-1986 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - BLIS (Biblio-Techniques Library Information System)- Detailed Implementation Planning, 1985-1986 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - BLIS Negotiations, 1985-1986 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - BLIS Negotiations, 1985-1986 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - BLIS Negotiations-License Agreement, Purchase Agreement, 1985-1986 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - BLIS-Other Sites, 1984-1985 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - BLIS-Software Development, 1985-1986 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Statistics-Microcomputer Center, 1986-1987 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Statistics-Periodical Room, 1981-1982 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Statistics-ILL Summary, 1966-1974 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Statistics-COMPASS (Computer-Assisted Search Service), 1972-1985 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Statistics-COMPASS, 1972-1985 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Statistics-Interlibrary Loan, 1972-1986 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Statistics-Interlibrary Loan, 1972-1986 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Statistics-Reserve, 1954-1987 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Statistics-Reserve, 1954-1987 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Statistics-Reserve, 1954-1987 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Statistics-CAI, 1985 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Statistics-Cataloging, 1950-1963 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Statistics-Cataloging, 1950-1963 (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Statistics-Cataloging, 1950-1963 (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - Statistics-Coin Ops, 1983-1986 (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - Statistics-Coin Ops, 1983-1986 (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - Statistics-Coin Ops, 1983-1986 (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - Statistics-Coin Ops, 1983 (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - Statistics-Coin Ops, 1983 (Box 23, Folder 19)
  - Statistics-Coin Ops, 1983 (Box 23, Folder 20)
  - Statistics-Copy Service, 1963-1975 (Box 23, Folder 21)
  - Statistics-Copy Service, 1963-1975 (Box 23, Folder 22)
  - Statistics-Copy Service, 1963-1975 (Box 23, Folder 23)
  - Statistics-Copy Service, 1976-1981 (Box 23, Folder 24)
  - XCP, Inc.-Accounts, Receivables, 1980-1983 (Box 23, Folder 25)
  - XCP, Inc.-Accounts, Receivables, 1983-1985 (Box 23, Folder 26)
  - Olivetti Inventory, 1984 (Box 23, Folder 27)
  - Monthly Statistics, 1985-1986 (Box 23, Folder 28)
  - Olivetti Monthly Report, November 1985 (Box 23, Folder 29)
  - Olivetti Monthly Report, November 1985 (Box 23, Folder 30)
  - Savin/Mita Inventory, 1984-1985 (Box 23, Folder 31)
  - Mita 232 Monthly Report, November 1985 (Box 23, Folder 32)
  - Mita 232 Monthly Report, December 1985 (Box 23, Folder 33)
  - Biblio-Techniques BLIS, 1983-1984 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Biblio-Techniques-BLIS, 1983-1984 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Biblio-Techniques-BLIS, 1983-1984 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Circulation Policy Committee, December 1982 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Circulation Policy Committee, December 1982 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Information and Technology Section-Annual Report, 1983-1984 (Box 41, Folder 32)
  - Malawi-Correspondence, Reports, Floppy Disc- "Malawi Consultancy Documents,", 1991-1992 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Malawi-Correspondence, Reports, 1991-1992 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Malawi Libraries, 1988- 1998 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Malawi-Project Documents, University of Malawi Consultancy, 1992 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Malawi-Site Visits, University of Malawi Libraries, February 1992 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Malawi Triennial Review, April 28, 1989 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Malawi Triennial Review (2nd), March 27, 1992 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Miscellaneous-Correspondence, Reports, 1992-1998 (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - National Science Foundation-Grant Proposals, 1989-1992 (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - National Science Foundation-Grant Proposals, 1989-1992 (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - National Science Foundation-Grant Proposal Background Information, 1991 (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - National Science Foundation-Grant Proposal Background Information, 1991 (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - NOTIS-Appendices, Reports, 1984-1984 (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - NOTIS-Appendices, Reports, 1983-1984 (Box 24, Folder 19)
  - NOTIS-Appendices, Reports, 1983-1984 (Box 24, Folder 20)
  - NOTIS- "Public Online Catalog and Research Libraries Final Report, 1982-09 (Box 24, Folder 21)
  - Periodical Room Survey-Raw Data, 1985-05 (Box 24, Folder 22)
  - Periodical Room Survey-Raw Data, 1985-05 (Box 24, Folder 23)
  - Periodical Room Survey-Raw Data, 1985-05 (Box 24, Folder 24)
  - Photocopy System Analysis-Correspondence, Reports, Data, 1988-1996 (Box 24, Folder 25)
  - Public Services Professional Staff Meetings, 1988-1989 (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - Public Services Professional Staff Meetings, 1989-1990 (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - Public Services Professional Staff Meetings, 1992-1993 (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - Public Services Professional Staff Meetings, 1994-1995 (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - Public Services Professional Staff Meetings, 1995-1996 (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - Public Services Professional Staff Meetings, 1997-1998 (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - Public Services Professional Staff Meetings, 1998-1999 (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - Public Services Professional Staff Meetings, 1999-2001 (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - Public Services Professional Staff Meetings, 2002-2005 (Box 43, Folder 9)
  - Reference Meetings, 1990-1991 (Box 43, Folder 10)
  - Reference Meetings, 1991-1992 (Box 43, Folder 11)
  - Requirements Report, November 1983 (Box 24, Folder 26)
  - Requirements Report, November 1983 (Box 24, Folder 27)
  - Wells Women's Institute Bibliography, [n.d.] (Box 24, Folder 28)
- Series VI. Building Projects
  - Correspondence-Building Project, 1983-1993 (Box 41, Folder 31)
  - Correspondence-Entomology Library Move, 1984-1986 (Box 41, Folder 31A)
  - Correspondence-State University Construction Fund (SUCF) (1), 1983-1986 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence-SUCF (2), 1986-1988 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence-SUCF (3), 1988-1991 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence-SUCF (4), 1992 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence-SUCF (5), 1992-1994 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence-SUCF (6), 1994-1998 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Architect Information-Edward L. Barnes; John M. Y. Lee, 1986-1991 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Book Security; Network, 1990-1992 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Building Ideas-Equipment Access and Lighting, 1987-1992 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Collection Development-Materials Used in Addition, 1992-1998 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Environment and Utility-Safety and Disaster Preparedness, 1992-1998 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Equipment Requirements, From Office for Capital Facilities (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Interiors-Correspondence-Mann Library Addition and Loading Dock (1), 1993-1997 (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - Interiors-Correspondence-Mann Library Addition and Loading Dock (2), 1997 (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - Interiors-Correspondence-Mann Library Addition and Loading Dock (3), 1997-1998 (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - Interiors-Project Scope Documents (1), 1997-1999 (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - Interiors-Project Scope Documents (2), 1998-2000 (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - Mason Report-Facilities Program Plan for Expansion and Renovation of Mann Library, April, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 18)
  - Meeting Minutes, Bailey Hortorium and Mann Building, 1992 (Box 25, Folder 19)
  - Program Phase Report, 1992 (Box 25, Folder 20)
  - Schematic Phase Report, Correspondence, 1993-03-26 (Box 25, Folder 21)
  - Responses to Schematic Phase Report, 1993-02-08-1994-08-01 (Box 25, Folder 22)
  - Space Descriptions-Mann Library Departments, 1992 (Box 25, Folder 23)
  - Staff Involvement-Ed Ostrander-Moving Information, 1983-1992 (Box 25, Folder 24)
  - Statistics on Mann Library and Other Libraries, 1988-1990 (Box 25, Folder 25)
  - Mann Library-Addition Plans (1), 1993-2000 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Mann Library-Addition Plans (2), 2000 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Mann Library-Renovation-PDC (Planning, Design Construction), 2000 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Addenda #1-#5-Gary L. Wood Drawings, 1996-01 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Bid Sets with Addenda 1, 3, and 5, 1996-01 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Building Demolition-Asbestos Sampling/Testing Survey Report, 2000-01 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Design Manual-Correspondence, 1987-1994 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Design Manual-Correspondence, Comments, 1994 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Design Manual-Correspondence, 1994 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Environmental Impact-Correspondence (1), 1987-1994 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Environmental Impact-Correspondence (2), 1993-1994 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Environmental Impact-Correspondence (3), 1993-1994 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Final Environmental Impact Statement, 1994-10 (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - Lead Sampling/Testing Report, 2000-01 (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - Planning Background - Building and Interiors (1), 1999-2000 (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - Planning Background-Building and Interiors (2), 1999-2000 (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - Renovation Planning, 1997-2001 (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - Design Manual Phase Report, 1993-11-30 (Box 26)
  - Design Manual Phase Report, Appendix C, 1993-11-30 (Box 26)
  - Specifications-Volume 1, Division 1-14, 1996-01-16 (Box 26)
  - Specifications-Volume 2, Division 15 and 16, 1996-01-16 (Box 26)
  - Programming Methods in Design, 1997 (Box 41, Folder 33)
  - Mann Library Addition Records-Correspondence, Studies, Reports, Floor Plans, etc., 1993-2001 (Box 27)
  - Mann Library Addition Records-Correspondence, Studies, Reports, Floor Plans, etc., 1993-2001 (Box 28)
  - Mann Library Addition Records-Correspondence, Studies, Reports, Floor Plans, etc., 1993-2001 (Box 29)
  - Mann Library Addition Records-Correspondence, Studies, Reports, Floor Plans, etc., 1993-2001 (Box 30)
  - Mann Library Addition Records-Correspondence, Studies, Reports, Floor Plans, etc., 1993-2001 (Box 31)
  - Posters Announcing Renovation of Mann; S-100-S107- Color Coded Floor Plans, 2004-07 (Box 42)
  - Pre-construction Photographs on CDs, 2003-2004 (Box 41, Folder 34)
  - Mann Library Renovation Photographs on CD and DVDs, 2003-2006; CD #2160-2170; DVD #1153-1154 (Box 44)
- Series VII. Miscellaneous
  - Ornithology Library - Memos about including the Ornithology Library in the University Libraries System, 1970-1979 (Box 44, Folder 14)
  - Elfrieda Abbe-Inlaid Wood Panels (Box 41, Folder 29)
  - Program Offering-Dobis Leuven Library System, Third Edition, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Special Libraries Association (SLA), 1982-1983 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Agricultural College, History of Organization, 1958 (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - Agricultural Information Conference (International)- not completed, 1987 (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - AGRIS- International Information Systems (for the Agricultural Sciences and Technology), 1988-1989 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - CGIAR- Consultative Group on International Agricultural Research, 1988-1993 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Circulation Policy Advisory Group, 1984 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - CIT- Cornell Information Technologies, 1982-1988 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - CUL Advisory Committee, 1990-1991 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - CUL Departmental Libraries, 1962-1982 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - CUL- Preservation Policy and Planning Committee, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Elsevier- TULIP (The University Licensing Program) Working Plan, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Taking a Leadership Role in End-User Instruction, 1986-05-08 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - IITA- International Institute of Tropical Agriculture (Africa- L.D. Stifel), 1989 (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Mann Library History, 1986-1994 (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - Mann Library History (continued)- Photo: Mr. & Mrs. Philip Wagner with President Rhodes, 1986-1994 (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - Meckler/ALA Award- Mann Library Library of the Future Award, 1992-1993 (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - Meckler/ALA Award- Correspondence, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - Mann Library Procedures for Opening and Closing Building, 1959 (Box 10, Folder 32)
  - Mann Serials List Committee, 1992 (Box 10, Folder 33)
  - OTA- Office Technology Assessment (U.S. Congress), 1989 (Box 10, Folder 34)
  - Pergamon Press- Robert Miranda, 1989-1990 (Box 10, Folder 35)
  - Central Library Brochures, 1965? (Box 10, Folder 36)
  - Information Systems (Publication- Occasional Newsletter), 1987-1989 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Mann Library- Vocabulary List (Mann Orientation Program for New Staff), 1977, 1979 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Wisconsin, University of (Steenbock Memorial Library) Collection Development Policy, 1977, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - ACRL/ALA, 1983, 1984, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - Book Inventory, 1958-1987 (Box 11, Folder 34)
  - Boyce Thompson Institute, 1972-1979 (Box 11, Folder 35)
  - Chinese Agriculture, 1983-1987 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Compass, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Instructional Computing, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Industrial Innovation Service, 1985 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Mann Library Goals, 1982-1988 (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - Mann Library Handbooks and Guides, 1952-2008 (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - Other Library Handbooks and Guides, 1968-1973 (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - Mann Library-Social and Staff Committee, 1971-1991 (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - Mann Library-Social and Staff Committee; Reference staff (2004), 1970-1987 (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - Mann Library-Events and Projects (VIVO, Core Agricultural Literature Project), 1993-2005 (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - Mann Library-Endowment Campaigns, 1993-1998 (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - Mann Library-Publications: "Mann Daily Planet", 2000 (Box 13, Folder 30)
  - Equipment Needs, 1980-1981 (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - "Major Goals of Agricultural Research and Extension Education Programs"-Resident Teaching (Box 22, Folder 20)
  - Recognition Certificate, 1978 (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - Coding Charts and McBee Cards, 1980s (Box 44, Folder 8)
  - Library Policies and Performance Appraisal Forms (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Emergency Action Plan, [n.d] (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - Leave Card, Book Request Card, Timecard, [n.d] (Box 44, Folder 11)
  - Theses Classifications, List of Journals Once Kept in Periodical Room, [n.d] (Box 44, Folder 12)
  - Photograph of Back Room, [n.d] (Box 44, Folder 13)
  - List of Cornellians who lost their lives on September 11, 2001 (Box 46)
- Series VIII. Manuals
  - Circulation Night Supervisor Manual, 1980s (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - Notis Manual, 1986 (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - Circulation/Reserve Assistant Manual, 1986 (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Circulation/Reserve Department Procedures Manual for Reserve, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Circulation/Reserve Assistant Manual, 1988 (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - Student Manual, 1985 (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - Student Manual, 1988-1991 (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - Mann Library-Bindery Procedures Manual, 1993 (Box 41, Folder 30)
- Series IX. Awards
  - Scrapbooks documenting the Ari van Tienhoven Award, 1987-2011 (Box 45)